screengeek.net 2018-10-05

# Privacy - ScreenGeek

ScreenGeek.net maintains a firm commitment to you, our readers, privacy. 

The following policy dictates our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, ScreenGeek.net. Please be sure to continue to check this page occasionally, as we will continue to update this policy as is needed. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use ScreenGeek.net. By accessing or using ScreenGeek.net, you agree to this privacy policy. We welcome any and all questions, comments, and suggestions. Please contact us here with any questions. 

This policy applies to information we collect on ScreenGeek.Net and via e-mail and other electronic messages between you and ScreenGeek.net. It does not apply to information collected by any third party (including our affiliates), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser(s) may place or recognize cookies on your browser. Companies that place ads on ScreenGeek.net may also use their own cookies to help determine the frequency and placement of particular ads. Your browser controls how cookies are used and can be set to not allow them. 

For purposes of this policy, personally identifiable information is your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, or other information that you may voluntarily provide to ScreenGeek.net. ScreenGeek.net will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone. ScreenGeek.net contains links to other websites. Although we do not provide any personally identifiable information to these companies, we cannot guarantee your privacy once you leave ScreenGeek.net. ScreenGeek.net is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of websites with links on our site. 

ScreenGeek.net may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement personnel, government officials, or others when we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent violations of the law, injury to person or property, or any harm to ScreenGeek.net or others.

ScreenGeek.net  is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any Personal Information to or on ScreenGeek.net. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

We collect certain limited information from and about users of ScreenGeek.net automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including details of your visits to ScreenGeek.net, including traffic data and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on ScreenGeek.net, and information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data. It helps us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
